The first question asked was: Will this code work
as written? The answer? No. I will run this code,
and we get an error message that the file is not
readable. Why is that? Look at the mode on line 6.
The w means write, not read. The second question
in the exercise asked what one change was needed
to make this code work. You may recall that a
plus sign added to the file opening mode makes
a file both readable and writable. Of course, you
will want to be careful with this setting so you
don’t accidentally overwrite a file that should
be read. But I will add the plus sign after the w,
rerun the code, and now, everything works
as intended. Note: While "w+" allows for
both reading and writing, it truncates the file,
wiping out its existing contents to start with
a clean slate. This behavior occurs because
writing is the primary operation associated
with "w". If you're looking to read and write to
an existing file without deleting its content,
you can use "r+". In this mode,
reading is the primary operation,
and it allows you to both read from and write to
the file while preserving its current content.